"use strict";

const capital = [
  [
    {
      question: "Capital of Abia",
      option: ["Adamawa", "Yola", "Umuahia", "Akwa Ibom"],
      answer: "Umuahia",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Adamawa",
      option: ["Gombe", "Maiduguri", "Cross River", "Yola"],
      answer: "Yola",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Akwa Ibom",
      option: ["Benue", "Bauchi", "Uyo", "Akwa Ibom"],
      answer: "Uyo",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Anambra",
      option: ["Awka", "Jigawa", "Birnin Kebbi", "Lokoja"],
      answer: "Awka",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Bauchi",
      option: ["Kwara", "Ikeja", "Bauchi", "Lagos"],
      answer: "Bauchi",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Bayelsa",
      option: ["Yenagoa", "Enoch", "Damaturu", "Abeokuta"],
      answer: "Yenagoa",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Benue",
      option: ["Rivers", "Jalingo", "Makurdi", "Zamfara"],
      answer: "Makurdi",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Borno",
      option: ["Maiduguri", "Taraba", "Oshogbo", "Minna"],
      answer: "Maiduguri",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Cross River",
      option: ["Kebbi", "Calabar", "Cross River", "Ekiti"],
      answer: "Calabar",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Delta",
      option: ["Katsina", "Asaba", "Lagos", "Port Harcourt"],
      answer: "Asaba",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Ebonyi",
      option: ["Ebonyi", "Abakaliki", "Oshogbo", "Port Harcourt"],
      answer: "Abakaliki",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Edo",
      option: ["Benin City", "Akure", "Borno", "Uyo"],
      answer: "Benin City",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Ekiti",
      option: ["Yobe", "Ado Ekiti", "Ibadan", "Ekiti"],
      answer: "Ado Ekiti",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Enugu",
      option: ["Delta", "Nasarawa", "Ekiti", "Enugu"],
      answer: "Enugu",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Gombe",
      option: ["Gombe", "Makurdi", "Dutse", "Benin City"],
      answer: "Gombe",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Imo",
      option: ["Gombe", "Kebbi", "Imo", "Owerri"],
      answer: "Owerri",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Jigawa",
      option: ["Bayelsa", "Borno", "Yenagoa", "Dutse"],
      answer: "Dutse",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Kaduna",
      option: ["Bauchi", "Maiduguri", "Kaduna", "Umuahia"],
      answer: "Kaduna",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Kano",
      option: ["Umuahia", "Ado-Ekiti", "Kano", "Awka"],
      answer: "Kano",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Katsina",
      option: ["Ado-Ekiti", "Jigawa", "Benue", "Katsina"],
      answer: "Katsina",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Kebbi",
      option: ["Jos", "Damaturu", "Birnin Kebbi", "Ibadan"],
      answer: "Birnin Kebbi",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Kogi",
      option: ["Abakaliki", "Owerri", "Kaduna", "Lokoja"],
      answer: "Lokoja",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Kwara",
      option: ["Jalingo", "Ilorin", "Imo", "Ebonyi"],
      answer: "Ilorin",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Lagos",
      option: ["Abeokuta", "Mushin", "Sokoto", "Ikeja"],
      answer: "Ikeja",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Nasarawa",
      option: ["Lafia", "Maiduguri", "Ado-Ekiti", "Nasarawa"],
      answer: "Lafia",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Niger",
      option: ["Jigawa", "Abakaliki", "Minna", "Lokoja"],
      answer: "Minna",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Ogun",
      option: ["Kebbi", "Ilorin", "Abeokuta", "Birnin Kebbi"],
      answer: "Abeokuta",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Ondo",
      option: ["Asaba", "Ondo", "Akure", "Ado-Ekiti"],
      answer: "Akure",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Osun",
      option: ["Oshogbo", "Bayelsa", "Calabar", "Yenagoa"],
      answer: "Oshogbo",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Oyo",
      option: ["Niger", "Ibadan", "Lagos", "Owerri"],
      answer: "Ibadan",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Plateau",
      option: ["Adamawa", "Ogun", "Nasarawa", "Jos"],
      answer: "Jos",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Rivers",
      option: ["Asaba", "Edo", "Enugu", "Port Harcourt"],
      answer: "Port Harcourt",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Sokoto",
      option: ["Lokoja", "Ikeja", "Sokoto", "Lafia"],
      answer: "Sokoto",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Taraba",
      option: ["Taraba", "Jalingo", "Lagos", "Ibadan"],
      answer: "Jalingo",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Yobe",
      option: ["Damaturu", "Oyo", "Yobe", "Osun"],
      answer: "Damaturu",
    },

    {
      question: "Capital of Zamfara",
      option: ["Plateau", "Damaturu", "Gusau", "Ibadan"],
      answer: "Gusau",
    },
  ],
  {
    quizTime: 45,
  },
];
